<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>El Met</title>
    <link>https://ramonmacias.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on El Met</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ramonmacias.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Tech Book Club</title>
      <link>https://ramonmacias.github.io/2023/04/21/tech-book-club/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonmacias.github.io/2023/04/21/tech-book-club/</guid>
      <description>It takes something more than intelligence to act intelligently. &amp;ndash; Fyodor Dostoyevsky
Proposal This is one of the cultural initiatives that our company has undertaken. The purpose of this confluence page is to comprehensively document all aspects related to our book club, including the reasons for its existence, the methodology we use, and the activities we engage in. Our objective is to track the books we read and record all the insights generated during our discussions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Auth Middleware in Go</title>
      <link>https://ramonmacias.github.io/2020/10/19/auth-middleware-in-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonmacias.github.io/2020/10/19/auth-middleware-in-go/</guid>
      <description>We’re just enthusiastic about what we do. &amp;ndash; Steve Jobs
Proposal I have many reasons why I fell in love with Go, when I started working with go there wasn&amp;rsquo;t too much packages at that moment, so basically you needed to built everything from scratch, this was a great experience because I learnt a lot of basic concepts related with client and server comunications, that I didn&amp;rsquo;t learn before in other languages because we used big frameworks such as Spring in Java.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spaceship Shooter Game</title>
      <link>https://ramonmacias.github.io/2020/06/27/spaceship-shooter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonmacias.github.io/2020/06/27/spaceship-shooter/</guid>
      <description>90% of what is considered &amp;ldquo;impossible&amp;rdquo; is, in fact, possible. The other 10% will become possible with the passage of time &amp;amp; technology. &amp;ndash; Hideo Kojima
Game Probably one of the main motivation that I had when I was young, was the passion for video games, and this leads me to explore what is now my current professional career, computer engineer. Of course my main focus when I was young, is just play for fun, basically most of time I was thinking on having fun and nothing more, but is also true that sometimes I realised how real are some games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Limit/Offset</title>
      <link>https://ramonmacias.github.io/2020/04/26/limit-offset-pagination/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonmacias.github.io/2020/04/26/limit-offset-pagination/</guid>
      <description>The computer was born to solve problems that did not exist before. &amp;ndash; Bill Gates
Pagination One of the most common feature that we will face at some point as a backend engineer, is how to deal with pagination on the server side. Exists different ways for implement that, and as you can imagine, each one has it good and bad points. On this post I will try to implement the most basic one in Go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to my blog</title>
      <link>https://ramonmacias.github.io/2020/04/13/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonmacias.github.io/2020/04/13/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>“Yeah It&amp;rsquo;s on. ”
Welcome and good morning! for all these people who is reading these lines and don&amp;rsquo;t know exactly why are you reading it, don&amp;rsquo;t worry I&amp;rsquo;m in the same boat. On this first blog post I want to talk a bit about my main blog&amp;rsquo;s goal and why I think this is going to be a great tool for me.
I have been working as a computer engineer for some time (not too much), over this period of time I learnt a lot of new things in a different ways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ramonmacias.github.io/top/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonmacias.github.io/top/about/</guid>
      <description>Life “If there is any one secret of success, it lies in the ability to get the other person&amp;rsquo;s point of view and see things from that person&amp;rsquo;s angle as well as from your own. Henry Ford”
My name is Ramon Macias, I was born in Manzanares Spain, but I moved to a small town in the middleware of the Catalan Pyrenees when I was 1 year old. The passion for computer science started when I had my first computer, and as you can imagine, I used it for play video games, I was fascinated about how all these games can simulate some parts of the real world, and all these years there we have been seeing the evolution on the video games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ramonmacias.github.io/top/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonmacias.github.io/top/books/</guid>
      <description>Machine learning学习笔记 Coursera 在线课程 Machine learning 笔记 讲师: 吴恩达(Andrew Ng) 课程地址：https://www.coursera.org/lear</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
